SADAF MOIN

OBJECTIVE

To explore my energies and talent for achieving self-realization, to satisfy appetite for challenges and considerable practical experience. To contribute towards the growth and development of a dynamic organization where opportunities to grow both professionally and personally are ample.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Proficient with MS Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.

Charismatic and confident public speaker.

Bilingual – Fluent in English and Urdu.

Have good communication and coordination skills.

Passionate for work and have driven to deliver.

Capable of working under pressure, result oriented and a good team

leader.

EXPERIENCE

INTERNSHIP, ABBASI SHAHEED HOSPITAL

17-12-2012 - 17-01-2013

I have been engaged in prescription monitoring, development of pharmaceutical plan, care, problem solving and also have active participation in medical team.

SEMINARS

WORLD PHARMACIST DAY

September 25, 2013 – September 25, 2013

Sheikh Zayed Auditorium,

Karachi, Pakistan

DO YOU WANT AN ELEPHANT'S MEMORY? BY DR.DILBAR SAEED

September 12, 2012 - September 12, 2012

Pharmacy Auditorium, University of Karachi,

Karachi, Pakistan

AN ORANGE FEVER BY PHR.HUMA NASEEM

February 2, 2012 - February 2, 2012

Department of Pharmaceutical Chemistry, University of Karachi,

Karachi, Pakistan

APPLE DAY CELEBRATION

October 21, 2011 - October 21, 2011

Department of Pharmacognosy, University of Karachi,
Karachi, Pakistan

PHARMACY: A CHARUSMATIC ROAD TO SUCCESS BY PHR.S.IRFAN AHMED

April 9, 2011 – April 9, 2011

Research Institute of Pharmaceutical sciences, University of Karachi,
Karachi, Pakistan

UNIVERSITY OF KARACHI- KARACHI- BECHELORS IN PHARM-D

My graduation is in progress with current CGPA 3.4. (2011-2015)

KHATOON-E-PAKISTAN GOVERNMENT COLLEGE FOR WOMEN- KARACHI- INTERMIDIATE

I have done my intermediate in PRE-MEDICAL in 2010 and have obtained A grade.

EVEREST GRAMMER HIGH SCHOOL- KARACHI- MATRIC

I have done my Matric in SCIENCE in 2008 and have obtained A1 grade.

ACHIVEMENTS Appreciation for active participation in the maintenance services rendered in faculty during May 2011- August 2011.

REFERENCES References can furnish on requirement

EDUCATION